a couple months ago I committed to doing
a live video every day I think two
people came on my livestream and scared
me and I haven't been on them since and
they in no way you've been attracted
with me it was just the fact that they
were there when I was used to talking to
myself
feeling like my hands are gonna be in
the camera it's different than on
periscope so a bit on periscope I've
been because people can randomly find me
but it's never gonna have the audience I
need it's never gonna have we're
probably not gonna have YouTube and
Facebook are the two social media
platforms that they actually no more
time I like where I want to spend my
time and therefore if I'm watching other
people's YouTube videos why not comment
or even here but then there's no content
here because I haven't been here I want
to find my collaborators I want to find
the people who want to create the
technology company that's gonna save
humanity that even if it's a fraction of
the burning passion that it is in me I
don't need them to be as dedicated as me
it's my it's it's my vision that will
become our vision as other people's
ideas are incorporated in it so I'm
going to show up on YouTube I have been
keeping up with my blog post for the
last few weeks writing them on Mondays
and now that that's become a little more
routine keeping that up I'm going to at
least do for YouTube every week reading
my blog post which is both easier for me
because I don't have to UM feel
inadequate that I'm not able to edit the
videos I can just go live and read it
and unstop and that's one of the reasons
I've been on periscope is because
YouTube isn't really the place to have
unedited videos without thumbnails
without and I'm not able to do that at
the moment and so until someone else
comes on board with our tech cooperative
who's able to do those things this is
what happens it's just gonna be me
talking on camera without an edited and
I need to be okay with that I needed to
feel like it's okay
to show up in this way in a space where
everyone else is more professional
because the mission I've been tasked
with the passion the idea the thing that
is inside me getting out requires it
requires that I keep putting myself out
there in new ways and do you know what
scares me without allowing it to stress
me out and that is a hard hard balance
to find but I'm finding it and I'm
learning how to talk from my heart
instead of my brain because all the
stuff that I'm doing is very logic
intellectually based but what I but it's
so that we can tap into our hearts so we
can tap into communities so we can
create the technological solutions that
help us collaborate on a massive scale
that we own together because when we own
it together it acts differently it
doesn't have the pitfalls that our
current technology has where it's us
versus them and they are doing things
are not an our best interest we can
create what is in our best interest
humanity's best interest and create the
tools to be able to understand to be
able to collaborate and so I'm going to
short more I'm going to be on YouTube
read my blog post I'm going to not
commit to coming on live daily but I
will be on more often as I have a topic
I won't be on for two hours like I go on
periscope for I will still be on
periscope but creating this channel so
that it can possibly it will it will get
more subscribers if I show up and just
be me with my idea I will find the
people to collaborate with the people
who I don't need to convince everyone
that we can dismantle capitalism and
create a world of abundance for every
single human being I
that to be a spark in 1% one of the
thousand people they that see it which
means then that many people have to see
it but I just need to find the handful
of people who can see the vision so we
can create the first project and they
can help home the message with editing
with more of a script and I need to
allow it to happen
which means showing up showing up on
YouTube and showing up on Facebook the
two that are more powerful for what I'm
trying to do which is create a community
that's going to create the technology
company it's going to save all of
humanity thank you